天呐  那辆好像是她的车
Oh, my God. I think that's her car.
好了大伙儿  都让开点
All, right, guys! Keep it clear.
你们就没别的事可做了吗
Don't you have anything better to do?
曼迪  曼迪
Mandy, Mandy!
曼迪  你分手以后跟扎克说过话吗
Mandy, have you--have you spoken to Zach since the breakup?
你后悔劈腿吗
Do you regret cheating on him?
传言说你又回戒毒所了
Is there any truth to the rumor
是真的吗
that you're going back into rehab?
卡塞尔
Castle?
我该担心你对我们婚约的承诺吗
Should I be worried about your commitment to our engagement?
不该  干什么
No. Why?
报纸上写着
'cause it says right here
你要跟前妻复合了
that you're getting back together with your ex-wife.
-什么  -就这儿  第六版
- What? - Right here. Page six.
卡塞尔被撞见跟出版商前妻拥抱
"Castle caught cuddling with ex-wife publisher."
不不  这是工作午餐
No, no, this was a business lunch.
我们在谈希特和斯道姆系列丛书的事
We were discussing Heat and Storm books.
所以你没有
Oh, so, um, you weren't...
深情凝视她的双眸
"Gazing lovingly into her eyes"?
她牙里卡了菠菜  这可真是  好吧
She had spinach in her teeth. That's just--okay.
我真不  你看  要是你让我
I don't--see, this wouldn't happen
宣布咱们订婚了  这种事怎么会发生
if you just let me announce our engagement.
我们早就谈过了
We already talked about this.
我们生命中重要的人都已经知道了
Everyone that's important to us already knows.
是的  我是公众人物
Yes, and just because I'm a public figure
不代表你也要成为公众人物  我明白
doesn't mean you need to be one, too. I know.
正是
Exactly.
只要你不介意发生这种事
Well... As long as you don't mind this sort of thing happening.
我不介意  又不是真的
I don't. 'cause it's not true.
这只会给我更多折磨你的材料
And it only gives me more material to torture you with.
青出于蓝胜于蓝啊
Mm, and the student becomes the master.
谁大清早6点45分按别人家门铃啊
Who rings the doorbell at 6:45 in the morning?
C先生  但愿没吵醒你
Hey, Mr. C.! Hope I didn't wake ya.
没有
No.
我正要去上班
I was just on my way to work,
就顺便来拿我的推荐信
thought I would pick up my letter of recommendation.
是啊  你那个经费申请
Right! For your grant, uh, application.
很感谢你帮我
Really appreciate you doing it.
我是跟阿丽克西斯说我写完了
I know I told Alexis I was finished,
但其实还没有
but I-I hadn't really quite, um...
我还在修改  一定要写好
I'm still tweaking it. This--I'm getting it just right.
你跟我一样  是完美主义者
You're a perfectionist, like me.
慢慢来  也别太慢了
Well, take your time-- not too much time.
今晚截止了
Deadline's tonight.
中午就能写好
I'll have it done by lunch.
谢了  C先生
Thanks, Mr. C.!
你最好了
You're the best!
我知道
I know.
派
Hi, Pi!
拜
Bye!
你一个字都没写  对吧
You haven't written a word, have you?
是的  但容我说一句  我要写什么
No. But in my defense, what am I supposed to write?
-那可是派  -那你为什么主动提出帮忙
- It's Pi. - So then why'd you offer?
我没有  阿丽克西斯拜托我的  我没法拒绝
I didn't. Alexis asked. I can't say no.
但不再多说借口了  我现在就写
But no more excuses. I'm gonna do it right now.
除非发生凶杀案了
Unless that's a murder.
我是专盯名人网的哈维·史崔克
This is Harvey Stryker with CelebGazer.com.
我们收到未经确认的消息称
We're getting unconfirmed reports that
流行天后曼迪·萨顿身亡  年仅22岁
pop diva Mandy Sutton is dead at 22.
曼迪·萨顿  不是吧
Mandy Sutton? Oh, no.
阿丽克西斯以前很喜欢她的儿童剧曼迪·曼乐迪
Alexis used to love her kids show, "Mandy Melody".
她白天是个普通的青少年
She was a regular teen by day
晚上就化身为打击罪案的歌星
and a crime-fighting pop star by night.
但学校里的人都不知道  因为她白天戴眼镜
But no one recognized her at school because she wore glasses.
看来她这招也该用在现实生活中
Well, it looks like she could've used that trick in real life.
看看这些人  难怪她生活一团糟了
I mean, look at this. No wonder she was such a mess.
警探
Detective!
能为我们确认曼迪·萨顿的死讯吗
Can you confirm for us that Mandy Sutton's dead?
我...
I, you know...
能说说她是怎么死的吗
Can you give us any details about how she died?
我得走了  还要做事  抱歉
I gotta go. I have work to do. Sorry.
理查德·卡塞尔
Oh, hey, Richard Castle.
你要跟前妻复合的消息是真的吗
Is it true that you're getting back together with your ex-wife?
今天的主角不是我
This isn't about me today.
卡塞尔
Uh, Castle?
你为什么不否认
How come you didn't deny it?
否认什么  刚刚的事吗  开什么玩笑
What do you mean? Back there? Are you kidding?
要是否认了  他们就该以为是真的了
Yeah, if I deny that, then they think it's true.
你不是说不介意吗
I thought that stuff didn't bother you.
是不介意
It doesn't.
曼迪就住这栋楼吗
So Mandy lived in this building?
是的  顶层公寓
Yeah, penthouse.
门卫今早六点前发现的尸体
Doorman found her just before 6:00 this morning.
吸毒过量吗
O.D.?
鉴于她的生活方式  大家都这么以为
Given her lifestyle, you'd think.
但这是简单的老派谋杀
But this is plain old-fashioned murder--
脑后钝器伤
blunt-force trauma to the back of the head,
面部撕裂伤可能是倒下时造成的
the facial lacerations probably happened with the fall.
死亡时间呢
Okay, when did this happen?
尸斑表明是昨晚9点到11点
Lividity puts it between 9:00 and 11:00 last night.
可以少算一小时
Well, we can cut that time frame in half.
门卫说昨晚十点
Doorman said that the limo dropped her off
豪华轿车把她送到大堂
to the lobby last night at 10:00 p.m.
她回家后一小时内就被杀了
She was killed within an hour of returning home?
她来这里干什么
What was she doing back here?
门卫也不知道
Doorman didn't know.
但他说有时她想躲避人群
But he said that she uses that door sometimes
就会走这扇门
when she wants to avoid the crowd.
也许她是要偷溜出去  或者约见某人
So maybe she was sneaking out or meeting someone?
要真是这样  凶手可能就是她认识的人
If so, it was probably someone she knew.
两边的门都锁上了
Gates are locked on both sides.
得有密码才进得去
You need an access code to get in.
有保安监控录像吗
Is there any security cam footage we can pull?
这边没有
Not back here.
真是讽刺  她一生都暴露在闪光灯下
Ironic, seeing as how she spent her entire life
却死在没有监控录像的地方
in front of cameras.
昨晚屋外有狗仔队盯着
Paparazzi was out front last night.
去看看能不能拿到他们的照片
Let's see if we can get copies of their photos.
凶手有可能会被拍到
Whoever was behind this might've been in that crowd.
查清情况之前
And no talking to the press,
不要对媒体透露任何事
not until we know what's going on.
她在哪里  我的天  曼迪
Where is she? Oh, my god, Mandy!
-女士  -曼迪
- Ma'am? - Mandy!
女士  这里是犯罪现场  你不能过来
Ma'am, this is a crime scene. You can't be back here.
我...你不明白  我是她的私人助理
I--you don't understand. I'm her personal assistant.
你还是不能过来
You still can't be back here.
但我们会请你去局里录笔供
But we will need to take you to the station to get a statement.
你有她亲属的联系方式吗
Do you have contact information for her next of kin?
她...她的经理人
That would be her-- her manager.
我是说  她妈妈
I mean, her mother.
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
她去小巷子做什么
What was she even doing in that alley?
你知道有什么人想要伤害你女儿吗
Do you know of anyone that would've wanted to harm your daughter?
当然
Yeah.
很多人不喜欢她  因为她改变了形象
A lot of people disliked her, who she became,
暴露的衣服  热辣的舞风
her provocative clothes, and dancing.
他们只想让她永远做"曼迪·曼乐迪"
They just wanted her to be little "Mandy Melody" forever.
她最近有没有接到什么人的恐吓
Had she received any threats recently?
有的  她收到过一些令人不安的信
Sure, she'd get some disturbing letters.
但侵略性太强的
But any that were too aggressive,
我们都移交给保安公司了
we'd turn over to the security firm.
好的  所有这类信件我们都要过目
Okay, we're gonna need to see all of those letters.
你知道昨晚她有约什么人
Now do you know if she was planning on meeting
在公寓见面吗
sith anyone at her apartment last night?
我们已经两天没有跟她说话了
We hadn't spoken to her in two days.
她失踪了吗
She was missing?
不  我们知道她在哪里
No, we knew where she was.
通过社会媒体和八卦网站不难了解她的行踪
It wasn't hard to track her on social media and gossip sites.
她这几天疯狂地参加派对
She was partying pretty hard.
过去几个月  曼迪真的很乖
For the past few months, Mandy'd been doing really great.
上回戒毒回来之后  她再也没沾过那东西
She stayed clean since her last stint in rehab.
她甚至有了新的男朋友
She even met a new guy
是做社区服务的时候认识的
while she was doing her community service.
扎克
Zach.
他为穷人搭建房屋
He builds houses for the poor.
几天之前  她去一个酒吧
And then a couple nights ago, she went to a club
参加某人的生日宴会  我猜就是那时候...
for someone's birthday, and I guess...
她喝多了跟前男友亲热
She got drunk and she started making out with an old boyfriend.
-被拍了照  -所有的八卦网站都登了
- And someone took a picture. - It hit all the gossip sites.
-扎克看到之后  -实在难以接受
- When Zach saw... - It was too much for him.
于是他们大吵了一架  他跟她分手了
They got into a big fight, and he left her.
他们约会了多长时间
How long had they been dating?
四个月
Four months.
这么说他知道怎么从楼后的小巷子
Which means he would know how to access the alley
进入你女儿的公寓
behind your daughter's building.
你知道去哪里能找到他吗
Do you know where we could find him?
说来可笑  我第一次看到这张照片的时候
It's funny. The first time I saw this picture,
还以为再没法感觉更糟糕了
I didn't think I could feel any worse
可是...现在她居然死了
but... now that she's gone...
是吗  你究竟有多难过
Yeah? Exactly how bad did you feel?
听着  我爱过她
Look, I loved her.
我绝不会伤害她
I would never hurt her.
那你不介意说说昨晚10点到11点
Then you wouldn't mind us asking where you were
你在哪里吧
between 10:00 and 11:00 last night.
不是我干的
I-I didn't do this, okay?
我那时在新纽泽西费尔菲尔德的一家木料场
I was at a lumberyard in Fairfield, New Jersey,
跟同伴一起装车
loading up a truck with the rest of these guys.
你可以去问问他们
You can--you can ask them.
你最后一次见她是什么时候
And the last time you saw her?
两天前我们分手的时候
Two days ago when I broke it off.
你们干嘛问我这些问题
Why are you asking me these questions?
你们怎么不去找那个被指控蓄意杀人的家伙
I'm not the one with the attempted manslaughter charges.
谁蓄意杀人
Manslaughter charge?
她的前男友  杰西·琼斯
Yeah, her ex-boyfriend, Jesse Jones--
就是照片里这个人
the one in that picture.
就是他教唆她吸毒的
He's the one who got her into drugs in the first place.
有件事曼迪没告诉任何人
And Mandy never told anyone this,
上次他们闹分手的时候
but the last time they broke up,
他曾威胁要杀了她
he threatened to kill her.
被控使用武器
Weapons charges.
暴力威胁恐吓
Aggravated assault.
罪名还真够多的啊  杰西
That's a hell of a resume, Jesse.
像你这样的人怎么会勾搭上超级明星曼迪的
How does someone like you hook up with a superstar like Mandy?
就跟其他来找我纹身的
Like all the other pretty little rich girls
漂亮富家女一样
that come to me for their ink.
她们想要的可比纹身多得多
She was looking for a lot more than a tattoo.
我来者不拒
I was happy to provide.
我从网上知道你俩轰轰烈烈过  但结果却很难看
So I read online that two of you were stormy and it didn't end well.
你砸烂了她的住处  还严重恐吓过她
You trashed her apartment and made some pretty serious threats.
都是老黄历了
Water under the bridge.
两天以前  你们两个又在一起了
Until two nights ago, when you guys hooked up.
怎么回事
How'd that happen?
我当时在一个酒吧  她进来了
I was at a bar. She came in,
向我投怀送抱  就跟以前一样
threw herself at me like old times,
我当然愿意"就范"
and I obliged.
那是我最后一次见到她
That was the last time I saw her.
那你怎么解释
How'd you take it
在你们的照片曝光之后
when right after that photo of you two appeared,
她对专盯名人网说你是个人渣
she told "Celebgazer" that you were... human trash...
那个晚上"她犯了人生中最大的一个错误"
and that that night was "The biggest mistake of her life"?
她当时看起来挺享受的
She seemed to like it okay at the time.
你昨晚10点到11点在哪里
Where were you last night between 10:00 and 11:00?
我跟朋友在皇后区的一个桌球房里
I was at a pool hall in Queens with some friends.
名字给我
Names.
蕾妮  怎么了
Lanie, what's going on?
我们这里有点小问题
We have a little problem here.
什么问题
So what's the problem?
我来告诉你
I'll tell you what the problem is.
这不是我女儿
That's not my daughter.
她不是曼迪
That's not Mandy.
曼迪的母亲证实死者是
So Mandy's mom identified our victim as...
克莱尔·萨缪尔斯  25岁  一名有抱负的女演员
Claire Samuels, 25. She was an aspiring actress.
-她是曼迪的替身  -替身
- And Mandy's decoy. - Decoy?
用来忽悠媒体的
Yeah, to fool the press.
这种手段在狗仔时代已经不出奇了
It's a practice not uncommon in this age of stalkerazzi.
她打扮成曼迪的样子
So she'd dress up as Mandy.
戴上墨镜
She'd put on sunglasses.
让狗仔们跟着她
She'd let the hordes follow her
于是曼迪就能神不知鬼不觉地离开了
so that Mandy could go about unnoticed.
我们通知了克莱尔的父母  他们正在赶来
Now we notified Claire's parents. They're flying in,
埃斯波西托这会儿正在调查她的情况
And Esposito's digging into her life as we speak.
如果克莱尔才是死者
So if Claire is our actual victim,
那么曼迪·萨顿去哪了
Then where's Mandy Sutton?
我们不知道  没人见到她
We don't know. No one has seen her,
她也不接电话
And she's not answering her phone.
鉴于克莱尔在被害时正伪装成曼迪
Given that Claire was pretending to be Mandy
那我们就得考虑到这种可能性
when she was killed, then we need to consider
那就是曼迪·萨顿
the very real possibility that Mandy Sutton
是凶手的预定目标
was our killer's intended target,
他们可能正在谋划实施
and that they might be looking to finish the job.
可能已经得逞了  所以我们才找不到她
They may already have, which is why we can't find her.
找到了  她在韦塞克斯酒店登记入住
Found her. She's checked into the Wessex Hotel
用的是她的一个化名
under one of her aliases.
但她没接房里的电话
But she's not answering her room phone.
敲门也没反应
And she's not responding to knocks on the door.
卡塞尔
Castle.
这不是血  是红酒
That's not blood. It's wine.
这么早就关门啦
Closing time already?
你谁啊
Who are you?
你说我死了  是什么意思
What do you mean, I'm dead?
克莱尔·萨缪尔斯昨晚被杀了
Claire Samuels was killed last night,
全世界都以为那是你
And the world thinks that that was you.
谁
Who?
克莱尔·萨缪尔斯  她是你的替身
Claire Samuels -- she's your decoy.
我们把她装扮成你  来混淆狗仔
The girl we dressed to look like you to confuse the paparazzi.
噢  这样啊
Oh. Oh, yeah, um...
天呐  那挺虐的
God, that's pretty harsh.
知不知道她昨晚为什么去了你的公寓
Do you know why she went to your apartment last night?
不知道  为什么这么问
No. Why?
我们想搞清楚
Well, I mean, we're trying to figure out
她是怎么去那儿的  你母亲说
how she got there, and your mom said
昨天不需要她给你做替身  所以...
that she wasn't scheduled to work yesterday. So...
豪轿公司说她当晚用的车
Yeah, uh, the Limo Company claims that the car
是你订的
she arrived in was ordered by you.
我从来没醉打过豪轿的电话  不过...
I've never drunk dialed a Limo before. But...
没有  不是我
Nope. Wasn't me.
克莱尔呢  你打给她了吗
What about Claire? Did you call her?
不  我都不认识她
No. I barely know her.
我们不鼓励私下联系
We discouraged personal contact.
如果她们两个被看到一起出去
It wouldn't make much sense to have a decoy
那要替身还有什么意义呢
if they're gonna be seen hanging out together.
我现在能躺下了吗
Can I lie down now?
萨顿小姐  我们还有几个问题
Actually, Miss Sutton, we still have a few more questions
有关你的生活
For you about your life.
我的生活
My life?
我们认为你可能成为了凶手的预定目标
Yeah, we think you may have been the intended target.
好吧
Oh, yeah.
这样就说得通了  问吧
That does make more sense. Okay.
你知道有谁想伤害你吗
So, um, do you know if anyone would have wanted to hurt you?
你有树敌吗
Do you have any enemies?
媒体  但是他们不会伤害我
The press, but... they wouldn't hurt me.
没有我  他们哪来的素材去写负面新闻
Without me, who would they write all those bad things about?
那前两天你在外面...
Okay, well, the last two days when you were out...
社交的时候  跟谁吵了或者惹了谁吗
socializing, did you have any fights or did you upset anyone?
可能吧
Probably.
我...  有点记不清细节了
I'm... a little hazy on the details.
好吧
Okay.
这就行了吧
Okay. That it?
暂时可以了  在此期间
Uh, yeah, for now. In the meantime,
你可能得回酒店
you should probably go back to the hotel and, uh,
待在房里保持低调
lay low in your room.
我们不能发个声明吗
Shouldn't we make an announcement?
让大家知道她没有死
Let everyone know that she isn't dead?
你们得知道  如果有人想杀她
Well, you know what? If someone was trying to kill her,
让他们认为已经得手会比较安全
it might be safer to let them assume
同时我们也在抓紧破案
that they've actually succeeded while we're still doing our job.
需要多久  她下周要开始巡演
How long? She starts a tour next week.
作为经纪人  我难以想象
And as her manager, I can't imagine that
如果大家都认为她死了  售票会成什么样
it's gonna help ticket sales if everyone thinks she's dead.
是啊  不想搞砸这次的复出大巡演
Yeah, wouldn't want to screw up the big comeback tour.
亲爱的  这些新歌你下了很大功夫的
Sweetie, you've worked really hard on those new songs.
我们是说  观望一天  可能更短
We're talking about staying out of sight for a day, maybe less.
很可能届时我们已经找到线索
Hopefully by then we'll have a lead that'll help us
找出幕后真凶了
figure out who's behind this.
贝克特
Uh, Beckett?
我找到线索了
I might have an idea about that.
粉丝来信中我们找到这封匿名信
We found this anonymous letter in her fan mail.
"我盯上你了  我不喜欢我所看到的"
"I'm watching you, and I don't like what I see."
这种人多了去了
Yeah, well, get in line.
伙计们  看看周围
Guys... look around.
我收到疯子来信  从不间断
I get letters from creepazoids all the time.
除了信以外
But in addition to the letter,
-他还附上了这些  -我的天
- He also included these. - Oh, my god.
这是我的卧室  趁我睡觉的时候
That's my bedroom, while I was sleeping.
你的公寓应该是很安全的
Your building is supposed to be secure.
他是怎么进去的
How did he get in?
这是喷墨打印纸
That's ink-jet paper.
所以呢
So?
所以我们可以追踪到
So we might be able to track it.
-怎么追踪  -大部分的人不知道
- How? - Most people don't know this,
用于打印照片的打印机
but the serial number of the printer that was used
它们的序列号其实是嵌入图片的
to make these photographs is actually embedded into the picture.
印成微小的小黄点
It's printed in tiny, little yellow dots
肉眼无法识别  这是联调局的技术
invisible to the naked eye. It's--it's an FBI thing
用于追踪伪造犯
Used to track counterfeiters.
我感觉不舒服
I don't feel so hot.
我看有人需要喝杯咖啡
You know, I-I think someone needs a cup of coffee.
你四份咖啡的拿铁
Here is your 4-shot latte.
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
鉴于我本该死掉
Considering I'm supposed to be dead,
应该算不错
about right.
我只是不敢相信居然有人进了我的卧室
I just can't believe that freak was actually in my bedroom.
我们会抓到他的
We'll find him.
我懂你的心情
I know how tough it can be--
狂热粉丝  时刻活在被人注视之下
the crazy fans, the constant scrutiny,
生活事无巨细的被人窥视的压力
the pressure of living your life under a microscope.
我是说  我也一样
I mean, I can relate.
虽然没你红  但还是
On a smaller scale, of course, but still, it's...
你  你是哪位
Wh-who are you?
比你不红太多
On a much smaller scale.
-爸  你在这  -阿丽克西斯
- Dad. There you are. - Hey, Alexis.
你怎么来了  是为派的推荐信吗
What are you doing he -- oh, the, uh, the letter for Pi --
只是  我正要  我还想修改一下
The -- I just, I'm about to -- I just gotta make a few tweaks.
-你还没写吧  -没完  好吧  没写
- You haven't written it. - Not all -- not yet.
我就知道你需要帮忙
I thought you might need some help...
所以我列了几个要点供你参考
so I came up with some talking points for you.
哦  挺好的
Oh, good. Okay, um...
出类拔萃  领导风范
"Outstanding person... natural leader."
爸  我知道你看不上派
Dad, I know you and Pi don't always see eye-to-eye.
你要是不想写
If you don't feel comfortable doing this --
没有的事
No, listen, hey...
我和派在一件重要的事上
Hey, Pi and I see eye-to-eye
见解十分一致
on one very important redheaded thing.
-就是爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you, too.
你听说曼迪·萨顿的事了吗
Hey! Can you believe that about Mandy Sutton?
-很奇怪吧  -确实
- It's weird, right? - Yes, weird --
还记得我多喜欢她的节目吗
Remember how much I loved her show,
还有秘密眼镜
and those secret identity glasses?
你生我气时  我就戴一副去吃饭
If you were mad at me, I'd wear a pair of glassesto dinner,
你就假装不认识我
and you'd pretend like you didn't know who I was?
-记得  事实上  -不过她长大就变了
-I remember, actually-- - but then she grew up.
真是的  真不明白一个人怎么就
And whoa! I mean, how does that happen to someone --
-变得这么不可救药呢  -我
- becoming such a hot mess? - I --
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
-我  以为你  -没错
- I... thought you were... - Yeah.
阿丽克西斯  这位是曼迪
Alexis, this is Mandy.
我们还在  保密她活着的消息
We're just, uh, keeping her under wraps for now.
这是我女儿
This is my daughter.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
爸  那不是真的
No, dad, it's not true.
我看了报纸
Yes, I know what they wrote.
订婚当然有效
We're still engaged.
什么叫特雷莎姑姑在脸谱网上发了状态
What do you mean aunt Theresa put it on her facebook?
那就让她删了
Well, t- tell her to take it down.
我得挂了  爱你哦
I gotta go. I love you.
拜拜
Bye.
埃斯波
Hey, Espo.
你会无条件的相信报纸吗
Do you believe everything that they write in the newspapers?
当然不  除了
Oh. Hell, no. I mean, except for that thing
卡塞尔和他前妻这事  那事
between Castle and his ex-wife. I mean, it's --
找到克莱尔的线索了吗
Did you find anything on Claire?
找到了
As a matter of fact, I did.
我调查了豪轿公司的电话记录
I went into the phone records of that limo company.
发现那晚叫车的
It turns out that Claire was the one
正是克莱尔
who ordered that limo last night.
克莱尔为什么叫车送自己去曼迪家
Why would claire order a limo to take her to Mandy's place?
不知道  刚跟克莱尔的室友通过电话
I don't know. But I just got off the phone with Claire's roommate,
说是克莱尔最近几天有心事
said Claire's been going through some things the last couple of days.
心情不好  一直哭
She's been upset... crying.
关于曼迪卧室的照片
Hey. Those photos of Mandy in her bedroom --
我查到了打印机序列号
I traced the printer's serial number
属于市中心一家电子商城
to an electronics store in midtown.
根据这份过期逮捕证
According to the extended warranty,
打印机是肯·卡斯特的
it belongs to a ken castor.
-他犯过事  -恶性袭击事件
- So he's done time. - For aggravated assault.
两年前
And then two years ago,
他因涉嫌跟踪曼迪·萨顿被签发了限制令
he was hit with a restraining order for stalking... Mandy Sutton.
本性难移
Old habits die hard.
这是她被害当晚的狗仔队拍摄的照片
And those paparazzi photos from the night that she was killed,
看我在上面找到了谁
I went through them. Look who was right there
正当克莱尔走出轿车时
when Claire stepped out of that limo...
同一个人
Same guy.
警察
Police! N.Y.P.D.!
厨房安全
Kitchen clear.
卧室安全
Bedroom clear!
壁橱
Hey. Closet.
放开我
Let go of me!
-放开我  -把手背过来
- Let go of me! - Gimme your arm!
我什么也没干
I didn't do anything!
-你还好吗  -嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
应该就是他了
I think we got our guy.
听着  你不明白
No, listen. You don't understand.
确实不明白
The hell we don't.
我们只知道这些是你拍的  肯
We know that you took those pictures, Ken.
还有你去过她卧室的事实
We know that you were in her apartment.
因为她需要我
Because she needed me.
需要你
Needed you?
我在保护她
I was protecting her.
我在守护她  她
I was watching over her, and she...
她需要守护
she needed that.
确实
Right.
因为以前都没人
Cause she didn't have people watching her
关注她
and staring at her already.
他们不在乎她
They didn't care.
没有我那么在乎
Not like me. They-- they...
他们不懂她
they don't understand her.
是他们把她变成这样的
I mean, they drove her to it, you know?
所以我寄去了那些照片
That's why I sent her the pictures --
因为她得知道还有人在乎她
because she needed to know that someone cared.
她  她得知道有人在看着她
She -- she needed to know that someone was watching.
你昨晚去她公寓也是为了看着她吗
Is that what you were doing outside of her apartment last night?
看着她
Watching?
我本可以救她一命的
I-I should have saved her.
但我没看见她
But I-I never saw her.
我...我等来了豪轿
I-I-I waited for the limo,
但出来的却是那个女孩
but then that girl came out--
不是曼迪  是那个女孩
the--the not Mandy, the other girl.
所以我绕到后巷去
So I-I went around to the back alley,
隔了条街守着
and I wait across the street.
通常那个女孩走前门的时候
When the other girl goes in the front,
曼迪就会从后门离开
that means that Mandy goes in the back.
但她没有
But... but she didn't.
等等  你在后门等曼迪出来
Wait, you waited for Mandy out in back?
是啊
Yeah.
你看到什么了吗
Did you see anything else?
你看见有人进出那条巷子吗
Did you see anyone go in or out of that alley?
只看见一辆摩托车
J-just the motorcycle.
等等  什么...
Wait a minute. What...
什么样的摩托车
What motorcycle?
就在我朝后巷走的时候
Well, right when I was going in the back,
有辆摩托车正开进巷子
there was a motorcycle that was going into the-- the alley.
什么时间
What time? When?
10点07
10:07.
我记下来了
I-I-I wrote it down.
我习惯把所有事情都写下来
I-I write everything down.
10点12离开的
And then at, uh, 10:12, it, uh, it left.
你看到车牌号了吗
Did you get a license plate?
没记下来  它开得太快了
I couldn't write it down. It was going too fast.
那骑车的人呢
What about the rider?
-你看到他的脸了吗  -他戴着头盔
- Did you see his face? - They were wearing a helmet.
我不知道曼迪在那儿
I-I didn't know Mandy was back there.
我是说  我根本没看到她出来
I mean, I-I never saw her go back, you know?
那摩托车呢
What about the motorcycle?
颜色  装饰
Color? Trim?
这我记得
I wrote that down.
是红色的  是辆红色的杜卡迪800
It was--it was red. It was, um...it was a red Ducati 800 supersport.
轮子是金色的  车身有火焰状的贴花
It had gold wheels, and it had a flame decal on the body.
-你怎么看  -他是个疯子
- What do you think? - He's a nut job.
但他很有可能不是凶手
But he's probably not our killer.
是嘛  你怎么知道
Yeah? How's that?
和狗仔不同  他知道轿车里出来的是克莱尔
Unlike the paparazzi, he knew Claire was getting out of the limo.
他能区分她俩
So he can tell them apart.
而他迷恋的是曼迪
And since he's obsessed with Mandy,
所以对克莱尔下手就说不通了
there would be no reason for him to go after Claire.
我们先扣留他
We'll hold him.
即便他不是凶手  也很可能是我们的最佳证人
But if he's not our killer, he's probably our best witness.
去调出这一带的交通监控录像
Why don't we get ahold of traffic cam footage in the area?
看能不能发现那辆杜卡迪的牌照
Let's see if we can get a plate on that Ducati.
金色车轮  车身有火焰贴花
Gold wheels, a flame decal on the body.
肯定是定制的
It's gotta be a custom job.
我去查查这一带的摩托车店
Yeah. I'll check with bike shops in the area,
看能不能找到做这类装饰的地方
see if I can find the place that did that work.
卡塞尔在哪儿
Where's Castle?
他在和他另一位前妻吃饭
He's having dinner with his other ex-wife,
说不想让她感觉受冷落之类的
Something about not wanting her to feel left out.
-编得好  -他窝在休息室
- Good one. - He's holed up in the break room
给阿丽克西斯的男友写推荐信呢
writing that letter for Alexis' boyfriend.
谢谢你
Thank you.
别担心了好嘛
Will you stop worrying?
他肯定会大大夸你一番的
He'll have lots of great things to say about you.
-我保证  -我不确定
- I guarantee it. - I don't know.
C先生并不怎么待见我
I'm not exactly Mr. C.'s favorate person.
再说这封信他确实写了很久
And he is taking an awfully long time.
他确实有其他事情要做
He does have other things to do, you know.
不  阿尔  我不是这个意思
No, Al, that's not what I meant.
他现在也许已经写完了
Maybe he's done by now.
他说写完就会给我发短信的
He said he'd text me when it was ready.
我看看
Let's see.
奇怪  我的手机关机了
That's weird. My phone's off.
这...不是我的铃声
That's...not my ring.
-喂  -你拿了我的手机
- Hello? - You have my phone.
曼迪  你好
Mandy? Hi.
对  我才发现
Uh, yeah, I just realized.
稀奇了  我们肯定是拿串了
Funny, we must have switched.
我要用手机  我在韦塞克斯酒店
I need it. I'm at the Wessex Hotel.
好  我没有故意拿你手机什么的
Okay. Sure. Oh, it's-- not like I took it on purpose or anything,
这只是个误会
just a misunderstanding.
房间号522
Room 522.
好 没问...
Yeah, sure. Not a...
喂
Hello?
我得去给曼迪送手机
I guess I'm bringing Mandy her phone.
我得去上城区
I-I gotta head uptown.
出现蜂蛹了  那我们回见
The bee pupae are emerging. See you later?
-好  再见  -再见
- Okay. Bye. - Bye. Oh!
嗨  你的手机
Hey, so, uh...here's your phone.
听着  我很抱歉之前说你"不可救药"
Look, I'm sorry about that whole "Hot mess" thing I said before.
抱歉你那么说了  还是抱歉被我听到了
Sorry that you said it, or sorry that I heard it?
我...可能该走了
I... should probably go.
你不注意的时候就会改变
It happens when you're not looking.
什么
Excuse me?
之前  你问起怎么会改变
Before... you asked how it happens--
怎么会变成我现在这样
how someone becomes like me.
不注意的时候就会改变
It happens when you're not looking,
等意识到的时候  就已经变成现在的样子了
And by the time you realize it, it's already who you are.
就好比路边发生了车祸
Like the car crash on the side of the road
所有人都停下来...观望
everybody stops and-- and watches.
这并不代表你非得变成这样
That doesn't mean it's who you have to be.
你总能改头换面的
You can always change.
事实证明我并不擅长改头换面
Turns out I don't do change so well.
但如果你要偷警车  要放火把它烧着的话
But...you steal a police car and you set it on fire
我是绝佳人选
I'm your girl.
或者找到世界上最好的男生
Or if you find the greatest guy in the world,
疯狂地相爱
Fall madly in love,
然后和我的人渣前任勾搭  把一切搞砸
and then mess it up by hooking up with my dirtbag ex?
这都是我能做出的事情
That I can do.
对  我在网上看见照片了
Yeah, I... saw that picture online.
全世界都看到了
You and the rest of the world.
或许如果你戒酒的话
Maybe if you didn't drink.
如果我戒酒  我就会有感受
If I don't drink, then I start to feel.
我不喜欢我感受到的
And I don't like what I feel.
我希望我有个"曼迪·曼乐迪"里的眼镜
I wish I had those glasses from "Mandy Melody".
我戴上它们  然后
I'd just put 'em on and...
就消失了
Just disappear.
我理解你的感受
I know how you feel.
你怎么可能会理解我的感受
How could you possibly know how feel?
因为现在  我
Because right now, I...
也希望可以从我的生活中消失
wish I could disappear from my life, too.
好的  谢谢  我回头会确认的
Okay, thanks. I'll check back.
派的推荐信写的怎么样了
So how's Pi's recommendation going?
写德里克·斯道姆小说都比这个好写
It took me less time to write the last derrick storm novel.
即使他们都是虚构的
And although they both are works of fiction,
至少那个有可信度
at least that one was believable.
案子进展的怎么样了
How's the case coming?
我们得到了从犯罪现场离开的
Well, we got a description of the motorcycle
那辆摩托车的描述  科技处正试着
that left the crime scene, and tech's trying to
从交通摄像头录像里找到车牌号
get a plate off of traffic cam footage,
但至今还一无所获
but so far no luck.
有收获了  我们找到那个混蛋了
Our luck just changed. We got the son of a bitch.
我们找到一家商店订制了
We found a shop that outfitted
一辆带有金色轮子和火焰贴花的
a red ducati 800 with gold wheels
红色杜卡迪800给一个叫乔什·格林伯格的人
and a flame decal for one Josh Greenberg.
这就是我们要找的人吗
Is that our guy?
乔什·格林伯格有点儿资金周转问题
Josh Greenberg had a slight liquidity problem.
所以他三天前把摩托卖了
So he sold that bike three days ago for cash
卖给了
To...
这个人
This guy.
杰西·琼斯  曼迪的前男友
Jesse Jones--Mandy's ex.
所以他对我们撒谎了  他在那个小巷里
So he lied to us. He was in that alley.
好了  把他带进来问话
All right. Bring him in.
我们已经派人去他家了
We already sent a car over to his place.
他不在那儿  曼迪应该能帮上忙
He's not there. Mandy might be able to help out.
她或许知道他常去的地方
She probably knows his hangouts.
好的  去吧
All right, go.
我和我男朋友的问题是
The thing about my boyfriend is...
我以为我成熟了
I thought I was being so grown-up--
和他同居  租套房子
moving in with him, getting my own place.
但现在这是我生活的一切了
But now it's my whole life.
我很确定我犯了一个巨大的错误
And I'm pretty sure I've made a huge mistake.
你知道我为什么要帮他申请经费
Do you know why I'm helping him with his grant application?
因为如果他得到了  他就要去旅行
Because if he gets it, he'll have to travel.
那太糟了  你得告诉他
That is messed up. You need to tell him.
告诉他什么
Tell him what?
说我改变主意了  说我想分手
That I changed my mind? I don't want a relationship?
我们是有租约的
We have a lease.
那真是太浪漫了
That's romantic.
而且这样对他太不公平了
And he doesn't deserve it.
他什么都没有做错
He hasn't done anything wrong.
哦对  还有我老爸
Oh! And then there's my dad.
我怎么跟他说
What do I tell him, huh?
说他从头到尾都是对的
That he was right all along,
我没有准备好
That I wasn't ready?
我倒是希望我那样说过
I wish I would have said that.
我没做好准备的事情多了去了
I wasn't ready for many things.
你没有回想过你自己做过的事情
Do you ever look back on something you've done
然后  觉得像是别人做的
and... it's like someone else is doing it?
你在开玩笑  对吧
You're kidding, right?
也是
Right.
对不起  我
Sorry, I...
没有可以谈心的人
haven't had anyone to talk to.
很明显
Clearly.
"做真实的自己"
"Be true to yourself."
扎克会这么跟你说
That's what Zach would say.
而且如果情况对你不利
And if a situation is bad for you,
就别管了  我们一般都会这样做
Leave it. That's what we were going to do.
也是你应该做的
And that's what you should do, too.
曼迪  有人给你发短信了吗
Mandy, is someone texting you?
奇怪  我应该已经死了
Weird, since I'm supposed to be dead.
是我的朋友萨姆
Oh, it's my friend Sam.
"非常确定你没有死
"Pretty sure you're not dead.
需要跟你说说死了的女孩
Need to talk about girl who died.
有些事情你需要知道
Something you need to know"?
等等  你在干什么
Wait, what-- what are you doing?
打给他  但你现在保持低调
Calling him? But you're supposed to be laying low.
没人应该知道你还活着
No one's supposed to know you're alive.
他已经知道我还活着了
He already knows I'm alive.
他以为你还活着
He thinks you're alive.
也许他只是想确认一下呢
He might be trying to find out for sure.
而且万一这不是萨姆
And what if it's not Sam?
也有可能是杀手想引蛇出洞
It could be the killer trying to lure you out.
别紧张  这是萨姆的号码  好吗
Would you relax? It's Sam's number, okay?
他没有接
And he's not answering,
说明他有可能在调酒
which means he's probably bartending.
他工作的地方很吵
That place he works is really loud.
我要去见他
I have to go see him.
你不能出去  万一被人看见怎么办
You can't go out. What if someone sees you?
你还是不明白  对吧
You don't get it, do you?
本该我死
I am the one that is supposed to be dead,
而不是克莱尔  她是因我而死
Not Claire. She died because of me.
我知道人们以为我不关心
And I know that people think that I don't care,
但我不是怪物
But I'm not a monster.
如果萨姆知道克莱尔之死的内情
If Sam has information about Claire's death,
我要知道那是什么
I need to know what it is.
我只是想做件正确的事
I just want to do one thing right.
曼迪
Mandy!
你不应该这样做
You shouldn't be doing this.
你阻止不了我
Yeah, well, you're not gonna stop me.
如果你执意要去
Okay, but if you're going to do it,
你不能被认出来
You can't be recognized.
懂了吗  你需要个人
Do you understand? You're going to need someone
帮你跟人说话
to do all the talking for you.
走吧
Come on.
曼迪不见了  去哪儿了
Mandy's gone?! Gone where?
还不知道
We're not sure.
前台的人没看见她走
No one at the front desk saw her leave.
有打斗挣扎的痕迹吗
Are there any signs of foul play?
没有  看起来她是自己离开的
Nah, it looks like she just took off.
说不定她又继续去寻欢作乐了
Maybe she, uh, picked up where she left off on that bender.
你们赶紧回来
You guys gotta come back.
我们得组织搜寻行动
We have to coordinate a search.
我们去问问轿车公司
We'll check with the limo company,
看她有没有叫车来接她
see if she called for a pickup.
我去问问她妈
And I'll talk to her mom.
我会列一张清单写明她平时喜欢去的地方
I'll get a list of all the places she likes to go to.
我们得在杰西发现自己杀错人之前
We have to find her before Jesse figures out
找到她
that he killed the wrong person.
怎么了
What?
发生什么事了
What happened?
曼迪呢
Where's Mandy?
你确定你真的要这样做
Are you sure I can't talk you out of this?
他在那儿  那就是萨姆
There he is. There's sam.
你疯了吗  你要干什么
Are you crazy?! What are you doing?
我来这就是为了帮你去叫他
That's what I'm here for.
萨姆
Sam!
嘿  萨姆
Hey, sam!
这样可是行不通的  小红发
That's not gonna get the job done there, Red.
你得脱几件衣服
You want to lose some layers?
把那种祖母戴的围巾给脱了
Take off Grandma's scarf.
我还有个主意
I have something else in mind.
然后她就问"你能相信吗"
So she was like, "Can you believe it?"
然后我就说"不可能"
And I was like, "No way."
真对不起
I am so sorry.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
萨姆是吧
Oh. Oh, Sam...Right?
能帮我再给她拿一杯吗
Can I please get her another drink?
还有…
Oh, and, um...
有人要见你
there's someone here to see you.
曼迪  天啊  真的是你吗
Mandy? Oh, my god, girl, is that you?
我们能去别的地方私下谈谈吗
Can we talk somewhere more private?
当然
Yeah, um...
去那儿等我吧
Y'all meet me over there.
你没事真是太好了
Yo, I am so glad that you're okay.
我很担心你
You had me worried.
我看到了你和杰西的那些照片
I saw those pictures of you and Jesse,
然后所有人都说你死了
then the next thing you know, everybody's saying that you're dead?
那你怎么知道我没死
What made you think I wasn't?
报纸上有张照片
That clip on the news--
拍到"你"昨晚在你家门前走下轿车
the one of the limo dropping "You" off at your building last night,
可那女孩并不是你
except that girl wasn't you.
你怎么知道的
How could you tell?
因为那个女孩
'Cause that same girl
昨晚来了这里
was in here last night
还穿着和她下轿车时一样的衣服
wearing the same thing she had on as when she got out of that limo.
等一下  克莱尔昨晚来了这里
Wait a second. Claire was here last night?
是啊  她应该是叫这个名字
Yeah, yeah. I think that's what her name was.
你和她说过话
You talked to her?
是啊  她是来找我的
Yeah, she came in looking for me.
她听说我和曼迪是朋友
She heard I was friends with Mandy.
她想要她的私人电话
She wanted her private number.
-为什么  -她找你是因为
- What for? - She was trying to reach you because
她觉得有人要伤害你
she thought somebody was trying to hurt you.
谁
Who?
她没说  但她一听我不肯给她你的号码
She didn't say, but she got way mad
就变得很激动
when I wouldn't give her your number.
我还以为这女孩疯了
Yeah, I... man, I thought this girl was nuts--
像那种疯狂的粉丝之类的
you know, a crazy fan or something.
然后她就问我怎么联系杰西
Then she asked me how she can get in touch with Jesse.
杰西  他和这事有什么关系
Jesse? What does he have to do with this?
我不知道  但…
I don't know, but...
她也很想跟杰西谈谈
She was pretty hot to talk to him, too.
所以我就打给杰西  让他们谈了
So I called jesse, and I put him on with her.
她说什么了
What'd she say?
我没听见  但她很不安
I didn't hear, but she was pretty upset.
后来她死了  所以我以为你该知道
And since she ended up dead, I thought you should know.
萨姆
Hey, sam!
等我一下
Wait here a second.
那儿有人渴了
People gettin' thirsty over there.
我不明白  克莱尔认识杰西吗
I don't get it. Did Claire know jesse?
不知道  我以为不认识
I don't know. I didn't think she did.
要弄明白只有一个办法
There's only one way to find out.
我要打给杰西
I'm calling Jesse.
等等  他可能参与了这事
Wait. He could be involved.
而且如果克莱尔觉得有人想杀你
And if Claire thought someone was trying to kill you,
打电话给他真的…
do you really think it's a good idea to call--
有人跟你朋友说过
Anybody ever tell your friend
她长得很像曼迪·萨顿吗
that she looks like Mandy Sutton?
是啊  经常有人这么说
Yeah, she gets that all the time.
曼迪的遭遇太令人遗憾了  对吧
It's a shame what happened to Mandy, isn't it?
那就是曼迪
Hey, that is Mandy.
我的天  曼迪·萨顿还活着
Oh, my god. Mandy Sutton is alive.
曼迪·萨顿还活着
Mandy Sutton's alive!
还是没有查到杰西的下落
There's still no word on Jesse's whereabouts.
曼迪也是  不过有个问题
Same with Mandy. But get this--
我打给轿车公司
when I called the limo company
想问问她今晚有没有叫车去酒店接她
to see if she ordered up a ride from her hotel tonight,
他们说她没有  但他们告诉我
they said she didn't, but they told me
我不是唯一一个问了这问题的人
that I wasn't the only guy asking that question.
-还有别人问了  -对  有个人说
- Someone else called? - Yeah, some guy who said
他是她经纪公司的
that he was with her management company.
但我查了  她公司没人打过这通电话
But I checked. No one there made that call.
-是杰西  -他可能发现了她还活着
- Jesse. - Maybe he found out that she was still alive.
大概所有人刚刚都发现了
Looks like everyone just did.
之前被认为已经死亡的
...that Mandy Sutton,
曼迪·萨顿还活着
presumed dead, may actually be alive.
有人称在闹市区一家叫猛禽夜店的夜店里
Mandy was reportedly just spotted at trendy downtown nightspot
看到了曼迪
the Raptor Lounge.
而且现在他还知道了该去哪找她
And now he knows where to find her.
喂
Hello?
是吗
Yeah.
在哪
Where?
我们得把她弄出来
We gotta get her out of there.
是的  我会派辆车去接她
Yeah. I'll send a car to pick her up.
我们还有一些
And we have some footage
由我们的观众在猛禽夜店
from the Raptor Lounge shot just moments ago
刚刚拍摄并上传的视频
and posted by one of our viewers.
卡塞尔  那不是...
Uh... Castle, I-isn't that--
那是阿...阿丽克西斯
That's Ale-Alexis.
她在那里干什么
What is she doing there?
我们得想法子出去
We have to get out of here. Uh...
这边走  来吧
Oh! This way. Come on.
我要给我爸打电话
Um, I'm gonna call my dad.
先走再说
Let's get out of here first.
说曹操曹操到  她来了
Speak of the devil, and she appears.
我得跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
我也是  上车
Yeah, same here. Get in.
我不确定那会是个好主意
I'm not so sure that's a good idea.
上车  你俩都上来
Get in, both of you.
下车
Get out.
下车  马上下车
Just get out. Out! Now!
过来
Get over here!
抱歉把你拖下水了
Sorry I dragged you into this.
我是来要答案的
Well... I want answers.
什么答案
Answers about what?
有人在整我
Someone is messing with me,
我知道你一定脱不了干系
and I know you're involved somehow.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
-别对我撒谎  -各位  冷静一点  好吗
- Don't lie to me! - Guys, let's just calm down, okay?
我相信没有什么是谈不妥的
I'm sure we can talk this out.
闭嘴
Shut up.
杰西  看着我
Jesse, look at me.
我犯了一个错
I made a mistake.
好吗  如果你认为
Okay, I-if you thought whatever happened
那晚我们之间发生的事
the other night between us meant that we were
代表我们可以复合  很抱歉
getting back together, I'm sorry,
那是不可能的
but that's not what's gonna happen.
你知道那天晚上
You know that wasn't you the other night
-照片里的人不是你  -什么
- in that photo. - What?
如果不是她  那她是谁
If it wasn't her, then who was it?
另一个妞  克莱尔
It's that chick, Claire.
有人出2万5千块让我跟她
I got paid 25 grand to show up and suck face
接吻以及被拍
with her for a couple minutes.
-你是说你真的不知道这事吗  -不知道
- You're telling me that you really don't know? - No!
那晚我醉得一塌糊涂  什么都不记得
I was messed up that night. I don't remember anything.
甚至不记得我是怎么喝醉的
I don't even remember getting messed up.
也许你不是喝醉
Maybe you didn't.
也许是有人给你下药  所以你没有记忆
Maybe somebody drugged you so you wouldn't remember.
然后让我看见照片
And then I-I would see the photos
以为那是我自己吗  杰西
and assume that it was me? Jesse...
你怎么能这样对我
How could you do that to me?
这跟你没关系  不再有关系了
This isn't about you, not anymore.
到底出了什么事  曼迪
What happened, Mandy?
谁杀了克莱尔
Who killed Claire?
我不知道
I don't know.
你这么关心是为什么
What do you care?
我关心是因为警察想把这事扣在我头上
I care 'cause the cops are trying to pin it on me.
那天晚上一定有人在巷子里看到我
Someone must have seen me in the alley that night.
等等  你在现场
Wait a minute. You were there,
-她被杀的时候  -我得跟她谈谈
- when she was killed? - I had to talk to her.
现在我们本该收到余下的2万5千块钱
Now we were supposed to get another 25 grand
只要照片登出来的时候
for staging that photo,
我们没有做任何动作
if we kept our mouth shut when the story ran.
都怪那婊子突然良心发现  对这一切
Only bitch got a conscience, felt bad about everything
都感到内疚  特别是那张照片
she had done, especially 'cause the pictures
害你和那个叫扎克分手了
broke up you and what's his name--Zach.
她非得去补救这一切
She just had to set things right.
这就是昨晚她想找你谈谈的原因
That's why she was trying to get in touch with you last night.
她打电话给我  说她要去你家
She called me and said she was going over to your place
把一切都告诉你
to tell you everything.
这代表我就拿不到余款了
Only that means I'm not gonna get my money.
所以我去找她谈话  希望能阻止她
So I go over there to talk her out of it,
就是这样
that's it!
我到那里的时候  她已经死了
And when I get there, she's dead.
杰西  如果你没杀克莱尔
Jesse, if you didn't kill Claire,
那就把枪放下
Then put the gun down.
我们可以一起去警局  把事情查清楚
We can go tohe police together and figure this out.
-我保证...  -你想唬弄我
- I promise... - You're trying to confuse me!
在我伤害你之前  把嘴闭上
Now shut up before I do something I--
马上转身  杰西
Turn around right now, Jesse!
把枪放下  杰西
Drop that gun, Jesse!
手  把手举起来
Show 'em! Show your hands!
蹲下  马上
Down! Now, now!
爸爸
Dad.
没事了  都结束了
It's okay. It's over.
如果杰西说的是实话  克莱尔是因为要
If Jesse's story is true, then Claire was about to reveal
戳穿照片是伪造的而被人谋杀
that those photos were fake and someone killed her for it.
也许克莱尔·萨缪尔斯
So maybe Claire Samuels
就是凶手的目标
was the intended target after all.
如果杰西说的是实话  悬
If Jesse's story is true. That's a big "if."
好的  谢谢  比尔
All right, thanks, Bill.
杰西这部分的话被证实是真的
So Jesse was telling the truth about this much--
五天前  他的确
he deposited $25,000 cash
往银行里存了2万5千块现金
in his bank account five days ago.
关于付钱的人有发现吗
Any more on who paid him?
没有  我们找到一张打印的纸条
No, we got a typewritten note
写着什么时候去酒吧见克莱尔
that told him when to meet Claire at the bar
以及进行交易的秘密地点
and where to find the money at a dead drop.
为什么会有人愿意付那么多钱
Why would someone pay that much money
来伪造这样一张照片
to stage a photo in the first place?
又是为什么这张照片如此重要
And what was so important about it
以至于有人竟然灭口克莱尔
that someone would kill Claire
以免被戳穿照片的真实性
in order to keep it from being exposed as a fake?
我不知道
I don't know,
但我知道有可能知情的人是谁
but I could think of someone who might.
各位  杰西有说
Guys, did Jesse tell you
照片是在夜店哪个位置被拍下的吗
where in the club that photo was taken?
内部闭路电视盲区
Somewhere in the back hidden from view.
为了保证没有目击者  不然早就流传出去了
Couldn't be any witnesses, or the gag wouldn't work.
所以那个拍照的人不是碰巧在那
So that photographer didn't just happen to be there.
他跟他们是一伙儿的
He was in on it.
拍照的人是谁
So who's the photographer?
詹姆斯·洛克哈特  你好啊
James Lockhart. How you doin'?
纽约警局  我们要问你几个问题  老兄
N.Y.P.D. We gotta ask you some questions, bro.
你俩能晚点再来吗
Listen, can you guys come back a little later?
你说什么
Excuse me?
有个女演员在咖啡店里  瑞丝·威灵福特
There's an actress in this cafe, Reese Wellingford?
我等了一个小时就为了等她出来
I've been waiting an hour for her to come out.
这可是刑事侦查  笨蛋
Listen, fool, this is a criminal investigation.
你卖给专盯名人网的那些照片
Who paid you to take those pictures
是谁雇你拍的
you sold to "Celebgazer"?
就是那张杰西·琼斯
The ones with Jesse Jones
和假曼迪·萨顿的合照
and the girl who wasn't Mandy Sutton?
没人雇我拍
Nobody paid me.
你是说  他俩在酒吧后边亲热的时候
Oh, really? So you just ended up in that backroom
你只是刚好在那  是吗
in that bar when those two hooked up?
是的  纯粹走运而已  她出来了
Yep, just lucky, I guess. Here she is.
在哪  我咋没看到  在哪呢
Where? I don't even-- is she over-- where is it?
你看到她了吗  我看不到  她--
Did you see her? I don't even see her. Is she--
是我挡镜头了吗  拍不到
Am I--am I in the way? Oh, you can't, uh, um...
糟糕  她走了  她在那呢
Oh, hey! Oh, there she goes. She's right there.
太可惜了  她上计程车了
Oh, no. Oh. She got in a cab.
好吧  我得到可靠消息了
All right, look, I got a tip, okay?
他们告诉我地点和时间  走到后门去
They said show up at such and such time, go in the back.
在保安撵我出来之前我拍了几张照片
I got a few shots before security threw me out.
谁给你透露消息的
So who gave you that tip?
-我不能透露  -警民合作嘛
- I can't tell you that. - I thought we were cool.
拜托  你们以为我会出卖我的线人吗
Oh, come on. You think I'm gonna rat out my sources?
我不会砸自己的饭碗
This is my livelihood.
你觉得如果我和我搭档跟你一整天
How do you think your livelihood's gonna go
你的饭碗还保得住吗
with me and my boy here following you around all day?
专盯名人网的哈维·史崔克透露给他的
Harvey Stryker from Celebgazer. com tipped him off?
他不只是把照片挂在网上
He didn't just run that photo on "Celebgazer,"
整件事是他策划的
he set the whole thing up.
为什么  难不成这混蛋不自己伪造点丑闻
But why? Doesn't this dirtbag have enough scandals to report on
就没有其他可以报道了吗
without having to make up his own?
因为这不只是一起丑闻
Because it wasn't just about the one scandal.
多年来  曼迪用她公众形象的毁灭
For years, Mandy has been drawing millions of eyeballs
酗酒的劣迹  进了康复中心
to "Celebgazer," with her public meltdowns,
为专盯名人网招徕了无数眼球
or drunken escapades, the, uh, trips to rehab.
但是过去的几个月  她很低调
But in the past few months, she calmed down,
她回到了井然有序的生活当中
got her life back in order.
因为她遇到了扎克
Because of Zach.
而这对他们的生意不利
Which was no good for business.
所以哈维拍了照  让曼迪回到
So Harvey staged the photo, turns Mandy back into the train wreck
糜烂的生活  好让他利用
that he grew to love and exploit.
这招很奏效  直到克莱尔扬言要
And it worked, too, until Claire was gonna ruin it all
将骗局昭告天下破坏这一切
by calling the photo out as a hoax,
摧毁哈维的名声
destroying Harvey's reputation.
所以哈维在公寓里
And that's why Harvey was at the apartment.
他不是在等曼迪  而是克莱尔
He wasn't waiting for Mandy. He was waiting for Claire.
他在等着杀她灭口
He was waiting to silence her.
假的  不  不  不可能
Fake? No, no, no, no.
专盯名人网才不造假呢
Celebgazer.com doesn't do fake.
你开了个先河
And yet you ran that one.
招了吧  哈维
Come on, Harvey.
我们知道整件事是你策划的
We know you set the whole thing up.
你雇佣杰西  然后收买克莱尔
You paid Jesse, then you paid Claire.
我没有收买任何人  克莱尔是谁呢
I didn't pay anyone. And who is Claire?
照片上的那女孩
The girl in the photo.
也就是威胁说要揭发你
The one that you killed right
之后被你杀了的那个女孩
after she threatened to expose you?
等等
Wait a minute.
我和这件事完全没有关系
I had nothing to do with any of this.
那你是怎么得到照片的
So then how did you get that photo?
我从一个自由记者的手上买的
I bought it from a freelancer.
我们和他谈过了
We spoke with him.
他说是你派他去那个酒吧的
He said that you sent him to that bar,
也就是说你知道克莱尔和杰西当时在那
which means you knew Claire and Jesse were there.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know?
用一贯的渠道知道的
The same way I always know.
有人向我透露的
I was tipped!
你以为我们会相信你的话吗
Do you actually expect us to believe that?
这是真的  我发誓
It's true! I swear.
我清清楚楚记得什么时候的事
I remember exactly when it happened.
他们打我电话  我可以证明给你们看
They called my cell. I can show you.
哈维给的那个电话来自一个一次性手机
Yo, that phone call Harvey got came from a burner phone.
用现金支付的
Paid for with cash.
所以他们在掩盖踪迹
So they were covering their tracks.
只是他们的技术太糙了
Yeah, only they didn't do a very good job of it.
忘了禁用GPS
They forgot to disable the G.P.S.
我们可以追踪GPS数据
We were able to track the G.P.S. data.
案子发生的那天晚上
Yeah. That phone was in the alley
那个电话在曼迪那栋楼后面的小巷里
behind Mandy's building the night of the murder.
所以买这个电话的人就是凶手
So then whoever bought that phone is our killer.
谢谢你们过来一趟  我们  我们只是想
Thank you for coming in. We, uh, we just wanted
让你们了解调查的最新进展
to keep you up-to-date on the investigation.
这么说是有新的进展了吗
So there's been a development?
是的  我们有新的线索
Yes, we have a lead.
我们已经识别出了
We've identified the cell phone of the person
策划假照片那个人的手机
that set up that fake photo.
而且我们相信这和杀了克莱尔·萨缪尔斯是同一个人
And we believe the same person killed Claire Samuels.
是谁
Who is it?
实际上  是个一次性手机
Well, actually, it was a burner phone.
一次性手机
A burner phone?
也就是说无法追踪到
So it's not traceable.
通常来说  是追踪不到没错
Uh, normally, it wouldn't be.
但是买了手机的这个人
But the person who bought this phone
犯了一个致命的错误
made one crucial mistake.
他们用完之后没有扔掉
They didn't get rid of it when they were done.
事实上  那个手机现在还开着
Matter of fact, it's still on right now.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom!
那张照片是你安排的
You set up that photo?
这一切都是你干的  你为什么要这么做
You did this to me? Why would you do that?
你为什么想要毁掉我的生活
Why do you wanna ruin my life?
毁掉你生活的人是扎克
It was Zach who was ruining your life.
我是在拯救你
I was saving you.
等一下  等等  你这么做
Wait a minute. Wait. You did this
是为了拆散我和扎克
to break me up with Zach?
他是我这辈子遇到的最好的事情了
He was the best thing that ever happened to me.
他准备带我离开这一切
He was gonna take me away from all of this.
是啊  带你离开我们一直努力奋斗得来的一切
That's right, away from everything we'd worked for --
你的巡回演出  你的事业
your tour, your career,
他会害你损失上百万的
he was gonna cost you millions.
你是说害你损失上百万吧
You mean cost you millions?
你放弃这一切是图什么呢
And for what?
过普通人生活的机会
A chance to be normal!
普通人
Normal.
你生来就与众不同
You're special.
扎克不理解
Zach didn't understand that.
克莱尔也无法理解
And neither did Claire.
所以你就把她给杀了
So you...killed her?
她要把我所做的一切告诉你
She was gonna tell you what I'd done.
她要让你恨我
She was gonna make you hate me.
我不能让她分裂咱俩
I couldn't let her drive a wedge between us.
我做不到
I couldn't.
玛丽莲·萨顿  请起身
Marilyn Sutton, please stand up.
转过身去
Turn around.
你因谋杀克莱尔·萨缪尔斯
You're under arrest for the murder
而被捕
of Claire Samuels.
曼迪  亲爱的  你理解妈妈的所作所为的  对吧
Mandy, sweetie, you understand, right?
我这么做都是为了你呀  曼迪
I did this for you, Mandy.
我做的一切都是为了你呀
Everything I did, I did for you.
不  妈妈
No, mom.
你这么做都是为了你自己
You did it for you.
走吧
Let's go.
正当我以为
Just when I thought
我的生活已经跌倒谷底了
life couldn't get any more messed up, right?
真是雪上加霜啊  媒体肯定爱死这种猛料了
And the train wreck continues. The press is gonna love this.
抱歉  我得走了
Sorry. I'm gonna go.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
曼迪  抱歉  我不是想要干涉你的生活
Um, hey, Mandy. Sorry, um, not to pry,
可我认为遇到这种事后  逃走躲起来
but, uh, it would be really easy just to run and hide
的确是很容易的选择
from all this.
但别这么做
But don't.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你们所做的一切
Thank you for all you guys did.
可不可以也替我谢谢阿丽克西斯
Um, could you thank Alexis for me, too, please?
我会的  她刚才还在这的
I will. Yeah, she was here.
我也不知道她跑哪去了  那个...
Actually, I don't know where she went. There's, oh --
我回来了  我还带了个人来
I'm back, and I've brought someone with me.
曼迪
Hey, Mandy.
扎克
Zach.
当我们发现曼迪其实并没有背叛他
Once we realized Mandy hadn't really cheated on him,
我就第一时间找到了他
I tracked him down.
我想他需要知道真相
I thought he needed to know.
干得好
Good.
我希望他们俩能有好结果
I hope it works out for them.
曼迪的生活中需要些正能量
Mandy needs something good in her life.
他们有机会的
They've got a shot.
他们俩好像真的很相爱
They seem to really love each other
单纯的相爱
for all the right reasons.
说到男朋友
Oh, um, speaking of boyfriends...
这是派的推荐信
Pi's letter of recommendation.
他把截止日期推后了  对吧
He did get the deadline extended, right?
是的  推后了
No, he did.
很好
Good.
"派"是哪个字  "苹果派"的"派"吗
How did I spell "Pi"? Did I put it like the dessert?
-因为我实在是不知道  -不  爸
- 'Cause that was just-- - No, dad.
-你没错  -那就好
- You got it right. - Okay.
我只是不太确定我没错
I'm just not sure I did.
你  你要去哪
Where -- where you off to?
我有点事要处理一下
There's something I need to do.
卡塞尔
Hey, Castle,
你的情感生活好像又见报了
looks like your love life made the paper again.
什么  好吧
Ah, what? All right.
好吧  我这次又跟谁好上了
All right, who am I hooking up with now?
"纽约本土小说家理查德·卡塞尔
"Novelist Richard Castle and New York police detective
和纽约本土警探凯特·贝克特
Katherine Beckett, both native New Yorkers,
今日宣布了他们订婚的喜讯"
are pleased to announce their engagement."
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
我没有  我
I didn't -- I did --
这不是我干的
I didn't do this.
事实上这是我干的
Actually, I did.
-你不是说  -我知道  卡塞尔  我注重我的隐私
- I thought you... - I know, I know, Castle. I like my privacy.
但是我意识到了你好歹算个名人
But I do realize that you're somewhat famous.
好歹算是个  我
Somewhat? I --
没错  如果我想和你在一起的话
Yes. And if we're gonna be together,
我就得学着接受并且适应这一点
I have to come to terms with that,
而且如果媒体非要爆你的料不可的话
and if they are gonna write about you,
我希望他们能爆些真材实料
I want it to be the truth.
我希望他们写的是咱俩
I want it to be about us.
你是我最希望...
Well, there's no one I --
你是我最希望和我一起等上头条的人了
There's no one I'd rather share a headline with.
但是为了准确起见
But just for the interest of accuracy...
这上面是不是说我们要在太空举行婚礼
does it say we're getting married in space?
没有  别做梦了  宝贝
No, it's not gonna happen, babe.
会很有趣的
Be pretty fun.
太空婚礼
Space.